[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9505_Skye_s01_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_02a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_02a",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_BeMyGuest_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9504_Shailyn_S01_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_X1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_X2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_X3",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_X3_EXPD_FireNaga_Complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_JT01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_02a",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_JT_01_TEMP_Talismans1_Incomplete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Temp"
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_JC01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Title",
        "Description": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@95_s01_JC_01_PERM_Cores1_Incomplete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ReleaseVersion": "Season_1_Perm"
    }
]
